

518-232-2116



lysenkoanton21@gmail.com



Cincinnati, OH



linkedin.com/in/anton-lysenkoll6

# **EXECUTIVE SUMMARY**

Anton got an introduction to programming in high school, where he fell in love with it. He has an understanding of computer architecture since his major in college was Electronic Engineering. Now, he is highly motivated to get a job in the software engineering field.

Anton's coworkers described him as determined, tenacious, and with the ability to learn quickly and who will not let down his team. In addition, Anton has an extensive experience in problem-solving, situation-handling, and accountability, which he mastered when had been managing two apartment complexes.

### TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML 5 **CSS** 

Bootstrap

JavaScript ES6

React

Express JS.

Node.js

REST

Mongoose

Mongo DB

Bash

# **Experience**

#### Salem Crown & Green Forest Apartments

Dayton, OH

2020 - 2022

Manager

- Entirely managed 54 one-bedroom apartments (2 complexes)
- Resolved property complaints and violations increased the rate of getting the 4+reviews by
- Implemented a new project task tracker and increased message response time by 85%
- Built relationships with service vendors and submitted associated billing statements.
- Completed all leasing steps (showings, applications, and verifications)

#### Salem Crown Apartments \*

Dayton, OH

2018 - 2020

Maintenance manager and renovation team member

- Built relationships with service vendors and submitted associated billing statements.
- Minimized costs by working and negotiating with multiple suppliers.
- Diagnosed and repaired technical issues.
- Worked extended hours when the company was short-handed

# **Education**

Per Scholas Software Engineering Bootcamp Cincinnati, OH

September 2022- Present

**Electronic Engineering** National Aviation University Kyiv, Ukraine

2014-2017 \*Degree Pending